# **Gauri Keluskar**

gaurikeluskar10@gmail.com

+91-8652578304 Bhandup, Mumbai, India

## **Summary**

I have 7+ Full Stack .NET Developer experience to lead the building of software using languages and technologies of the .NET framework. I have created applications from scratch, configured existing systems and provided user support. I have experience in the ASP.NET framework, SQL Server and architectural patterns/APIs also troubleshooting and resolving cross-platform/browser issues, performance optimization and other aspects of managing web server platforms. I have experience in managing multiple projects. I have experience in creating windows services. I have experience in banking domain.

#### **SKILLS**

C#.NET
ASP.NET
SQL SERVER, ORACLE SQL
WCF
ADO.NET
GIT
C#.net Windows Forms
JavaScript

#### **TOOLS**

Visual Studio 2017
SQL Server 2016
JIRA
Confluence
Postman
SQL Profiler
Oracle SQL Developer
Azure

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### -Senior Software Engineer

NCR Corporation India Pvt Ltd.

2018-Present

- Strong experience in C#, .NET 4.0, WebAPI (Rest, SOAP), MVC, EF, WCF.
- Strong experience in writing Stored procedures, complex SQL statements and Joins
- Experience in RESTful Http services design and development
- Hands on experience in Angular JS
- Experience with Team Foundation Server

- Experience of working with global teams
- Ability to work independently with limited supervision.
- Responsible for designing and solving complex technical issues related to the resolution of business problems and opportunities.

## -Software Engineer

NCR Corporation India Pvt Ltd.

2017-2018

- Worked in .NET Framework using C# (ASP.NET MVC, WebAPI)
- Experience with Web Services and serialization, XML, JSON, SOAP, WCF, REST
- Experience with JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap
- Experience with Agile Management Tools (i.e., Confluence, JIRA)
- Understand and implement best practices.
- Worked with other development teams for application development or integration across the globe and align development tasks with them.

# -Software Developer

Forbes Technosys Ltd.

2015-2016

- Analyzing user requirements, developing new software applications, or upgrading existing software in .net as per the business requirements.
- Writing well designed testable, efficient code in .net/SQL/T-SQL.
- Testing the product in controlled, real situations before going live.
- Preparation of technical documentation for users.
- Maintaining systems by monitoring and correcting software defects.

### - Software Developer

CMC Ltd.

2013-2015

- Development of new modules create excel/crystal reports as per business requirements.
- Migration of data

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science** 

University of Mumbai

2009-2013

## **NATIONALITY**

Indian